good night.
おやすみ
In sleep mode.
おやすみモードで
How was it, Itchi?
どうでした、イッチ?
It's been quite a while.
結構久々
It's been about a year already.
もう一年ぶりぐらいだったんですけど
TRUE?
本当?
It seemed to feel good.
気持ち良さそうだったもんね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's embarrassing when you say that.
そう言われると恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Oh, you took a shower.
あ、シャワー浴びてきたんだね
I don't think he will sleep at all because of this.
これでさすがに彼も寝ないと思う
I've done it many times.
何回もしちゃったもんね
I was really thrown out.
めっちゃ出されちゃった
A lot has been served.
出されちゃったね、いっぱい
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Not good.
よくない
Is that okay because it felt good?
そこは気持ち良かったからいいか
It felt good.
気持ち良かった
What did you do live?
生でしたことあんの?
There is no.
は、ないです
Ah, I see.
あ、そっかそっか
It's the flow.
流れだね
If it's a flow, then of course it's a sink.
流れだったら、当然流しとかもね
surely.
確かに
Oh, I'm sorry.
あ、ちょっとごめん
I feel a little anxious.
なんか不安はおるよ
It's probably okay.
多分大丈夫
perhaps.
多分
I don't know.
分かんない
That probably hasn't happened before.
そういうのは多分今までないから
What was good?
何が良かった?
Of cock.
チンポの
hard.
硬い
Was it hard?
硬かった?
hard.
硬い
It's really hard all the time.
なんかすごいずっと硬い
I liked that it was much harder.
ずっと硬いのが良かった
Which part was the best?
どの箇所が一番良かった?
All kinds of things like chin chin, pelar, etc.
い ろんな、チンチン、ペラーとか
Which one were you most excited about?
どれが一番興奮した?
Insertion that can be inserted?
入れられる挿入?
Is Chin Chin the best?
チンチンが一番?
It's okay, just get some rest.
全然いいわ、切りっくり休んで
I guess I like being a bit naughty.
ちょっとエッチ好きなんだね
I like it.
好きです
See you soon.
ちょっと またね
Let's do it.
やろうね
I'm not going to do it.
やろうって俺はやってない
Not with me either.
俺ともやってない
Can I ask you some questions?
色々聞いてもいいですか?
yes.
はい
How old are you now?
今はおいくつですか?
I'm currently 8.
今中8です
student?
学生?
I'm a student.
学生です
Are you a university student?
大学生ですか?
I'm a first year university student.
大学1年生です
1st year university student.
大学1年生
Do you want to graduate this year and enroll?
今年卒業して入学みたいな?
that's right.
そうです
high school?
高校?
Because I just got in.
入ったばっかりだから
I just got in.
入 ったばっかり
Is it fun?
楽しいですか?
Yeah, it's fun.
うん、楽しいです
What are you studying?
何を勉強してるの?
I like sports,
スポーツ好きで、
Study for that.
その ための勉強して
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
It's rare for a girl to play sports.
スポーツ珍しいね、女子女子で
What are you doing, sports?
何やってるの、スポーツ?
It's on Eric.
エリク上です
Ah, that's right
あ、そうな
of?
の?
Do you have a split in your abdominal muscles?
腹 筋とかで割れてる?
Yeah.
ええよ
But I don't really know because I don't really see it myself.
でもなんか自分であんまり見ないから分かんない
Ah, I see.
あ、そっかそっか
Eh, can I tell you how many generations?
え、何代とか教えてもいい?
Is that so?
そうなの?
It's a very famous place.
すごい有名なとこじゃん
That's serious, see you then.
ガチだね、じゃあね
Really?
ガチ?
It feels pretty serious, doesn't it?
結構ガチな感じだよね
Fairly.
割と
Pretty much around.
割と周りね
Oh, so it happened at a national tournament or something?
あ、じゃあなんか全国大会でだったとかしたん?
Well, I did.
え、しました
Really, then, oh, then it's early.
めっちゃ、じゃあ、あ、じゃあ早いんだ
Ah, but short distance?
あ、でも短距離?
Yeah.
うん
I'm good at it.
が得意です
Oh, short distance?
あ、短距離?
How many meters?
何メートル?
100 meters.
100メートル
Oh, that's amazing.
あ、すごいね
It's early.
早いんだ
early.
早い
I don't know.
分かんない
But it's me, my thighs are quite slim.
でも俺だね、太もも結構スリムな感じ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
That's right.
だ よね
Also, it doesn't seem to be very burnt...
あとあんま焼けてなさそうな...
I can feel it though.
感じはするけど
from now?
これから?
So, are you practicing hard every day?
え、じゃあ練習とか毎日頑張ってんの?
Practice, right?
練習、そうですね
hard?
大変?
No, but it's fun.
いや、でも楽しいから
not at all.
全然
TRUE?
本当?
Only men want to do two bodies, right?
二体やりたいとこ、男ばっかでしょ?
Oh, it's a mess.
え、めちゃめちゃいます
Awesome, isn't it popular?
すげー、モテるんじゃない?
Don't deny it?
否定せず?
Don't deny it.
否定はせず
What, do you want to confess something to your cousin?
え、何か告白されたいとこは?
I will.
しますね
Oh, so you have a boyfriend now?
え、じゃああんま彼氏いるんだ、今?
No, I'm not there right now.
いや、今いないです
What, aren't you going to make it?
え、作らないの?
Right now, I don't really think about it.
今はそうですね、あんまり考えてない
But the track and field team has a strong sexual desire.
でもその陸上部ってことは性欲強いよね
A little biased.
ちょっと偏見
That's very biased.
め っちゃ偏見ですね
That's pretty much it.
だいたいそうなんだよ
There may be nothing wrong with that.
あの別でも間違ってはないかも
Isn't it really strong?
よく強いでしょ?
Eh, what's going on?
え、どうなんですかね?
What, you don't have sex?
え、エッチはしないの?
In that private.
そのプライベートで
I only did it with the person I was wearing before.
前につけてた人とだけしました
Huh, how long is that?
え、それはいつくらい?
Do you only have a boyfriend?
彼氏としかしない?
I only do it with my boyfriend.
彼氏としかしないです
Well, what else?
え、それ以外は?
So it feels like it's been a while.
じゃあ久しぶりな感じだ
It's been a really long time.
めちゃめちゃ久しぶりです
Oh, is that so?
え、そうなの?
Sorry, I suddenly turned the camera like this.
ごめんね、なんか急にカメラをこう回しちゃって
No, I'm not used to it.
いや、なんか慣れてないんで
I agree.
そうだね
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしいです
Have you ever done any kind of gonzo?
なんかハメ撮りとかしたことある?
Wow, I'll only do it once.
うわ、一回だけやります
real?
ほんと?
I'm a little curious, I feel like this kind of thing makes me horny.
ちょっと興味あるんだ、やっぱこうムラムラするみたいな感じ
Right?
で しょ?
You mentioned it a little while ago.
ちょっと言ってたもんね、さっきね
It makes me horny.
ムラムラするって
I feel like I'd like to take a look at the older Chin Pum.
年上のチンポームがちょっと見てみたいな感じ
terrible.
やばい
Look straight up, this.
ちょっと真上向いて、これ
Looks early.
早そう
That's fine.
そうすればいいよ
This is a half-distance leg, right?
半距離の足でしょ、これがちょっと
I'm embarrassed, but please don't watch Gel Gel too much.
恥ずかしいんですけど、あんまりジェルジェル見ないでください
This is more muscular than this.
この程より筋肉だ、この
Run.
走るんだ
difficult.
難しい
Like this.
こうやって
If I were to be reborn, I would like to become a shoemaker.
生まれ変わるならシューズになりたいよ
And I'm already stepping on Pochinchin with my foot like this.
とか言って、これはもうポチンチンをこうやって足で踏んづけてる
But.
んです けど
Have you ever had that experience?
そう いう経験は?
No.
ないです
It looks like you're eating it.
食い気味だね
There's no way that's the case.
あるわけないよね
Can't you just do two?
2体だけはやんないの?
Can't you tell me this?
こういうの教えてくれないの?
No way
やんない
is.
です
It's been said for a long time that people who exercise have strong sexual power.
運 動してる人はね、性力が強いても昔からある話なんですよ、
Really.
本当に
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Really.
本当に
So you see, there are a lot of people who occasionally make it into the news.
だからほら、たまにニュースになっちゃったりする人たちいっぱ
Isn't it good?
いい るじゃない?
Maybe you're a teacher.
先生だとかで
Don't be.
ならないでよ
I'm worried.
心配されてる
Don't be a teacher.
ならないでよ、教え棒なんか
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Aren't you going to take me to the gymnasium or something?
体育倉庫とかに連れてくんじゃないの?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Really.
本当にね
As a pin, her style and attitude are also good.
ピンとしてやっぱりスタイル、姿勢もいいね
People who are exercising.
運動してる人は
I'm sorry, but I'm going to go to the wall for a moment.
せっかくだったってさ、ちょっとそこの壁のところ
As expected from a student, it's fashionable.
さすが学生だけあって、オシャレだね
I like fashionable things though.
オシャレはでも好き
Do you like fashion?
オシャレ好きなの?
It's just the belly button.
へそだしだもんね
yes.
はい
That hopeful body.
その期待めかれた、体が
Can you show me as far as your navel?
これへそぐらいまで見せられる?
Like this.
こうやって
Try raising it a little.
ちょっと上げてみて
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしい
picture,
え、
It's kind of amazing.
ちょっと すごいね
You have really big abdominal muscles.
なんか腹筋めちゃめちゃあるじゃん
What is Sabo?
サボってどれなの?
It's stylish.
オシャレだ
Well, even when I'm working hard, I still have a six-pack.
結構、あの、一生懸命やってるときもシックスパックとかいっちゃ
Right?
ってる でしょ?
Well, maybe during a tournament.
え、なんか大会のときとか
Six pack?
シックスパック?
After all, it's the belly of the athletic press conference.
やっぱ体育会見のお腹ですよ
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
So, your waist is small.
じゃあ、ウエスト細いもんね
a little bit.
ちょっと
picture?
え?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Isn't this skirt that one?
このスカート、あれじゃないの?
Aren't stones going to fall?
ストーンって落ちちゃうんじゃない?
The size has to be small.
サイズはちっちゃいのじゃないと
difficult.
難しい
Oh, you know, I don't understand muscles.
あ、これってね、筋肉が分かってない
Haven't you seen it?
見たことない?
No.
ないです
Me too, this is the first time I've said that.
僕もね、そういう、初めて言ってみたもん
My muscles are amazing now.
筋肉すごいし、今
Do you feel a little uneasy looking at it?
そう見ながらちょっとムラッとしてる?
I won't throw it away.
捨てない
Aren't you going to throw it away?
捨てないの?
I won't throw it away.
捨てないです
This place used to be a hotel.
ここね、昔ホテルですからね
Let's raise our abdominal muscles abnormally here.
腹筋異常に上げてみましょうか、ここ
It's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいんですけど
Oh, that's embarrassing.
え、恥ずかしい
Ah, this is the underwear of someone who is aiming for an athletic press conference.
あ、これが、体育会見に目指してる人の下着ですよ
No way.
やだー
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Can I watch it for about 2 hours?
2時間くらい見てていい?
Like this.
こうやって
I don't have it.
持たないですよ
持たない
I'll have it.
僕は持つよ
I haven't watched it for two or three hours.
2時間でも3時間でも見てないよ
I think it will go up, right?
上行くと思うじゃないですか
I'm going down first.
下行っちゃうんですよ、先に
The upper one and the lower one are embarrassing.
上の方と下の方が恥ずかしいんだよ
Well, both are embarrassing.
え、どっちも恥ずかしい
Both are embarrassing.
どっちも恥ずかしい
Let's go either way.
どっちかで行きましょう
Eh, which one?
え、どっち?
The one below is embarrassing.
下の方が恥ずかしい
The bottom one is better, so let's start from the top.
下の方がさ、じゃあ上から行きましょう
So, how about making it a little more stylish?
じゃあ、ちょっとオシャレにしとくの?
Here, like this.
ここ、こうやって
Right.
ね ー
Do it like this.
こうやってね
Yes, there is something like this.
あるよね、こういうのね
That's fine.
いいですよ
tickles?
くすぐったい?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
Shall we go downstairs?
下も行っちゃいましょうか
Is it underneath too?
下もですか?
It might be embarrassing.
恥ずかしいかも
A little while ago, this kid.
ちょっと前で、この子
And it's bright.
しかも明るいもんね
picture,
え、
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
Isn't it okay to think of this as a sports bra?
これスポブラだと思えばよくない?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Your body is hot, isn't it?
体はイッチだよね
It's really sexy though.
すごいセクシーなんだけど
I don't know, really.
わかんないです、ほんまに
I don't know.
わかんない
Well then, let's open.
じゃあ、オープンしちゃいますよ
Oh, that's embarrassing.
え、恥ずかしい
It's terrible, it's embarrassing.
やばい、恥ずかしい
Are you treating your armpits properly?
ちゃんと脇も処理してんの?
I will.
しますよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
a little bit.
ちょっと
This is the smell inside the body.
これが、日体内の匂い
It's terrible, it's embarrassing.
やばい、恥ずかしい
My neck.
首が
Hey.
ねえ
It's a big deal, isn't it?
すくせいでしょ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいね
During that time, I was touching your nipples.
その間にはさ、乳首触ってたらさ、
Your hips are moving.
腰動いてるよね
It's just my imagination.
気のせい
picture?
え?
Is it just my imagination?
気のせい?
I know, kind of.
わかってる、なんか
My eyes are getting dull.
目がウッドリしてきてるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですね
Does it feel good not to be touched?
触られんの気持ちいいの?
I don't know.
わかんない
Embarrassing, what is this?
恥ずかしい、なにこれ
It feels good.
気持ちいいじゃん
Hey.
ねえ
The beginning of my stomach.
お腹じまりと
terrible.
やばい
You wouldn't do something like this, right?
こういうことはしないでしょ、こういうことは
I'm pretty spot on though.
めっちゃ当たってるんだけど
Do you ever talk about sex like this with your friends?
友達同士でさ、こういうセックスの話とかしないの?
do not.
しない
Why not?
しないの?
You will.
するでしょ
You wouldn't.
しないでしょ
I don't.
しないんだ
Well then, you sullen.
じゃ、むっつりあなた
difficult.
難しい
That's very accurate.
すごい当たってる
It might fit through your pants.
パンツ突き抜けて入っちゃうかもね
That's terrible, isn't it?
やばいね、それは
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
This is that mouth.
こんなの、その口よ
It'll make you feel even more embarrassed.
もっと恥ずかしくなるんだから
It came off though.
外れちゃったけどね
Hey.
ねえ
When?
いつの間に?
Yes, before I knew it.
そう、いつの間に
Before I know it, I'll fall off.
いつの間に外れちゃうんですよ、僕
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
First time, first time.
初めて、初めて
Hi.
やあ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Isn't that a mess?
めちゃめちゃ、あれじゃない?
I'm putting a lot of effort into my thighs too.
うち股にも力入ってるじゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
But amazing, super abs, abs are showing.
でもすごい、超腹筋が、腹筋出てる
It's amazing, amazing, amazing.
もうすごいすごいすごい
Did I mention that I'll take care of the house by myself?
一人でうちのこともするって言ったっけ?
Hey.
ね え
yes.
はい
Oh, do you want to?
あ、する?
How often?
どれくらいの頻度で?
But a week, 2, 3.
でも週、2、3
That's a lot.
多いよね
I don't know.
わかんないね
It happened one day, right?
1日起きたことでしょ?
What does it feel like?
どういう感じ?
Yeah.
うん
Use toys or do it with your hands.
おもちゃ使うとか、手でやるとか
Boo.
ブーって
The one that says boo.
ブーってやるやつ
What to put in?
入れるやつ?
The one that trembles?
震えるやつ?
I can't enter.
入れない
Who can't enter?
入れないやつ?
The one that trembles?
震えるやつ?
Yeah.
うん
I'll use it later, then.
後で使うからね、それじゃあ
Oh no, it's embarrassing.
やだ、恥ずかしい
He said he was still wearing pankies.
まだパンキー履いてるじゃんだって
For those who have never shown it.
見せたことない人に
Hey, no, hey.
ねえ、やだ、ねえ
It's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいんだけど
Please don't look at me.
あんま見ないでくれ
Should I hold my chest?
胸つぶってよっか
This is Hiobi's big pussy.
これが日帯大のおまんこ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's moving extremely low.
めちゃめちゃ低く動いてるじゃん
Please don't say it.
言わないでください
It's better not to do live commentary.
実況しないほうがいいね
She has a thick pussy though.
肉厚なおまんこなんだけど
It's a wet mistake though.
濡れてるような間違いなんだけどね
Did you bring panties with you on your way home?
帰りのパンティ持ってきてる?
Are you bringing it?
持ってきてるの?
Are you holding up your panties?
持ち上げてるの、パンティ?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
this.
これ
I think the top of your panties is wet.
パンティの上は濡れてると思うよ
Oh no, it's embarrassing.
やだ、恥ずかしい
Oh no, it's ingrained in me.
やだ、染みついてそう
Please stop.
やめてください
It's ingrained in me.
染みついてるね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
May I have a look inside?
中までちょっと見せてもらおうかな
Messed up, that's it.
めちゃめちゃ、あれだね
It's stylish, your fingertips.
おしゃれだね、指先ね
That's it.
あれだね
I open it.
私が開いてしまう
No way.
やだ
I.
私
Use the strokes of the brush to make a strong impression.
筆筋使って、グッと
Yes, jerk.
はい、グッと
Try putting pressure on your stomach and get a jerk.
お腹に力を入れてみて、グッと
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すごい
Loosen up.
緩めて
Put your stomach in again.
もう一回お腹を入れて
Is it weird?
変ですか?
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
It's moving a lot.
すごい動いてる
Please try again.
もう一回お願い
It made a cute sound.
かわいい音出たね
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
しい
Wow, so erotic.
うわ、 エロ
Only a few people have been here, right?
ここ、数人しか入ったことないんでしょ?
yes.
はい
My clitoris is really moving, though.
めちゃくちゃクリトリスさ、動きしてますけど
No, don't say that.
やだ、言わないで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Don't be hungry.
お腹はないで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I keep saying bubble wrap.
どんどんプチプチ言ってる
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Please don't show it.
見せないでください
Is this a toy you have at home?
あなたが家にあるのは、このおもちゃですか?
Or is it a different toy?
それとも違うおもちゃですか?
It feels kind of similar.
なんか似てる感じ
It feels similar.
似てる感じ
That's different.
違うってことですね
Is this it?
これでは?
This isn't that.
これ、それではない
But to be honest, I'll give you this.
でも正直なんで、これ差し上げます
Wow, that's amazing.
え、 すごい
picture?
え?
It's very stimulating.
すごい刺激が強い
Ah, that's embarrassing.
あ、恥ずかしい
Great stimulation.
すごい刺激
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
My toes were like, Wow!
足の指さ、イエーイってなってたね
This felt good.
気持ちよかったもん、これ
Please show me that you hate me this time.
どうも今度、自分で嫌いって見せてくれ
Hey, it's embarrassing.
ねえ、恥ずかしい
Don't show it.
見せないで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Shall we take a look?
そろそろ見てみますか?
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
where?
どこ?
I saw it for the first time in a while.
私、久しぶりに見ました
Which is better for a woman, or a penis?
女にいいとさ、おちんちん、どっちの方がいい?
picture?
え?
I haven't done it recently either.
最近でもしてないから
Hey.
ねえ
Then try touching it.
じゃあ、触ってみて
Please feel free to touch it as much as you like.
どうぞ、触り放題
Looks like you took a lick, didn't you?
ちょっとなめたそうじゃない?
I just saw it that way, sort of.
今、そういう目で見たよ、なんか
It's just my imagination.
気のせい
気 のせい
But have you ever given a blowjob?
でも、フェラチョーしたことあるでしょ?
there is.
あります
What kind of blowjob do you give?
どういうフェラチョーすんの?
Let me just tell you this story for a moment.
ちょっと、ここだけの話で見せてよ
picture?
え?
Fellatio practice.
フェラチョー実習
It's been a long time.
めっちゃ久しぶりです
It's been a really long time.
め っちゃ久しぶりです
It's going to come out, in your mouth.
出ちゃうよ、これ、口の中で
That's an exaggeration.
大げさなの
picture?
え?
It's not an exaggeration.
大げさじゃないよ
This one's pussy.
おまんこの方
If you have a pussy, why don't you try putting this in there?
おまんこの方、ちょっとこれ、入れてみない?
picture?
え?
Just the tip, just the tip.
先っぽだけ、先っぽ
It’s been a while, hasn’t it?
久しぶりでしょ?
It's been a long time.
めっちゃ久しぶり
Only the tip.
先っぽだけ
Really just the tip.
ほんと先っぽだけ
Only the tip.
先っぽだけ
This is what the tip is like.
先っぽってこんなもん
Just the tip, look.
先っぽだけ、ほら
If only the tip.
先っぽだけなら
It's fine if it's just the tip.
先っぽだけならいいのね
I'm really wet though.
めちゃめちゃ濡れてるんだけど
why?
なんで?
I don't know.
わかんない
I'm going to get into this a little bit.
これ、もうちょい入っちゃうね
No way.
やだ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
If it feels good to be embarrassed,
恥ずかしいと気持ちいいだったら、
Which one is better?
どっちの方が上なの?
Both.
どっちも
Both?
どっちも?
But it's embarrassing.
でも恥ずかしい
I went all the way in.
奥まで入っちゃった
You can really see her pussy.
めちゃめちゃおまんこ見えてるじゃん
No way.
やだ
Don't look.
見ないで
It's in my pussy.
おまんこ入ってるさ
Can I take a look once?
ちょっと一回見ていい?
Awesome, amazing, amazing.
すごいすごいすごい
Air is coming out.
空気出てる
Does your penis feel good?
おちんちん、気持ちいい?
You'd better go in now.
もう入ったほうがいいよ
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Wow, it's been a while
すごい、久しぶ
the law of nature.
り
Ochinchin, it's been a while, Ochinchin.
お ちんちん、久しぶりだ、おちんちん
amazing.
すごい
amazing?
すごい?
Yeah.
うん
Can I go a little further?
もうちょっとずばずばしてもいい?
Doesn't it look like this?
こんなに見えでしょ?
You've been in there once, right?
一回入ってるでしょ?
amazing.
すごい
Amazing, even if you do it.
すごい、やらしても
Even if I show off my body.
体ずばずばしても
Can you move the most?
一番の動ける?
You want to move, right?
動きたいんでしょ?
Hey.
ねえ
Okay, look.
いいよ、ほら
amazing.
すごい
Please show me a little more about what's inside.
ずばずば入ってるのも、ちょっとよく見せて
It's a great push.
すごい押し出すね
Are you pushing me out like that?
そんな押し出すの?
My penis is the one that gets squeezed out.
おちんちん、それ絞り取られるやつなんだけど
Are both women and sex good?
女にとセクスさ、どちらもいい?
I said it.
言っちゃったね
Na
な
To?
に?
I'm brushing my teeth.
歯 磨きしてます
Are you brushing your teeth?
歯磨きしてます?
So just keep going.
じゃあそのまま続けてて
What what?
なになに?
It's okay, just brush your teeth.
大丈夫、歯磨きしてて
What what?
なになに?
There's a bit of a second shot.
2発目がちょっとあるんですよ
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってる
Would it have been better to shoot?
シュートしてるほうがよかった?
Is it better to not feel well?
元気ないほうがいい?
Isn't it better to have one?
あるほうがいいでしょ?
Why are you brushing your teeth?
なになに歯磨きしてる
It's okay, just break it.
大丈夫、そのまま折れ
Because I'm polishing it.
ちくり磨きしてるから
Everyone was shaking and shaking.
みんなシャカシャカしながら、ちくりながられて
Of the pussy.
おまんこちゃんの
Don't you want to brush your teeth without weight?
無重の歯磨きたいんじゃない?
Gargle.
うがいして
This movement, this.
この動き、これ
terrible.
やばい
Isn't it hard?
固いでしょ?
It's hard.
固いよ
It's early.
早いよ
early?
早い?
Isn't it hard?
固いでしょ?
It's a little wet though.
ちょっと濡れてますけど
It's a bit off topic though.
ちょっとどころじゃないけど
It's a little out of place.
ちょっとどころじゃないよ
Wouldn't it be better to give it another shot?
もう一撃しておいたほうがいいんじゃない?
One more time.
もう一回
Let's leave only one leg here.
こっちは片足だけ残っておこう
Wait a minute, this.
ちょっと、これ
This, this, this.
これ、これ、これ
Hey.
ねえ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
When I put dick in it, it immediately turns into a face.
チンチン入れたら、すぐ顔に変わってるんだけど
Is your shoulder still hurting?
ここまでしといて、肩がチンチンだめ?
It's not okay.
だめじゃない
In the end, we had sex.
結局、エッチしちゃったね
Even though I'm brushing my teeth.
歯まで磨いてるのにね
I did it.
し ちゃった
Let's take a bath and go home refreshed.
お風呂まで浴びてさ、それでさっぱりして帰ろうよ
You're wondering if he'll stand up again, right?
また立つんじゃないかと思ってるでしょ?
I'm right.
当たってます
Am I right?
当たりしてるのあって?
Did you understand?
分かったか?
I understand.
分かってる
What?
すって、何か?
I'm riding.
乗ってる
nice.
いいね
I'm standing nearby though.
近くに立ってるけどね
I'm already exhausted.
もうヘトヘタなんですけど
Exhausted?
ヘトヘタ?
This one isn't exhausted.
こっちはヘトヘタじゃない
You know, I'm already reacting like that.
ほら、もうそういう反応するから
yes.
はい
Are you doing it?
してるんですか?
Really?
本当に?
There's a camera, after all.
カメラはあるんだからね
If you see something slimy, that's it.
もし ヌグッとしたのがあったらあれだよ
Try raising it.
上げてみて
What is this?
これは何ですか?
What is this thread?
この糸は何ですか?
what?
何ですか?
Are you breathing now?
今、吐息があるんですか?
Should I give up on it now?
今、聞き捨てならない?
what?
何ですか?
That's it.
あれだね
It's out.
アウトだよね
That's what I'm saying.
言っちゃってるね
Is it the third round?
第3回戦ですか?
a little bit.
ちょっと
It's close, it's close.
近いよ、近いよ
He's talking.
喋ってるじゃん
Because it's hard.
硬いから
They say it's hard.
硬いと喋っちゃう
You're being serious.
本気出してるじゃん
You got serious.
本気になったね
You're getting serious, aren't you?
本気になってるじゃない
When that happens, it's a different story.
そうなってくると話が別だよ
I'm inside for a while.
ちょっと中入ってる
I've shaped the legs a little bit here.
ここにちょっと足もだいぶ形にしてて
What does it mean to tighten your hair?
髪を締め付けてるのはどういうことですか?
I can take this cock.
このチンチン取れちゃうよ
Oh, what about dying?
あ、死にて何?
What is it like to die?
死にて何?
Do you feel like you can go?
いけそうな気がする?
Yeah.
うん
You got permission.
許可出たね
If it happened every time, would you get angry?
もし毎回さ、出ちゃって怒る?
Let's go out.
出ちゃう
This is coming out.
これ出ちゃうぜ
Is it okay?
いいの?
It's the third shot though, so it's a little thin.
3発目だから薄いんだけど
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Isn't it transparent?
透けてない?
That's the one that makes me stand up.
それ立っちゃうやつなんだけど
Hey, maybe if I try to stand it up.
ね え、立たせようとしたらもしかして
a little bit.
ちょっと
I'll stand again.
また立っちゃう
Is that what you mean?
それつもり?
Isn't that so?
そうじゃないの?